<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Assignments on</title><link>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/</link><description>Recent content in Assignments on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 13:41:13 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assignment 1</title><link>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/assignment-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:43:20 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/assignment-1/</guid><description>Conway&amp;rsquo;s Game of Life # Conway&amp;rsquo;s Game of Life is a cellular automata simulation where a 2D grid of cells evolve between alive and dead states.
The Game of Life is a zero-player game, where you just set the initial state and the rules, and watch the evolution happen. A cell&amp;rsquo;s state in the next frame depends on the state of its immediate neighbors in the current frame. It is set by counting the number of live or dead neighbors and applying the corresponding rule.</description></item><item><title>Assignment 2</title><link>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/assignment-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:43:20 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/assignment-2/</guid><description>Video Effect # Instructions # Your assignment is to create an original video effect using openFrameworks and OpenCV. This will give you an opportunity to play with an image’s pixel data, and to get familiar with computer vision algorithms.
You can use some of the algorithms we covered in class (background subtraction, color tracking, etc.) or any other CV algorithm. Make sure to browse through ofxCv examples to see what is available to you!</description></item><item><title>Assignment 3</title><link>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/assignment-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:53:02 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/assignment-3/</guid><description>Depth Effect # Instructions # Your assignment is to create an original application using openFrameworks and a depth sensing camera. This will give you an opportunity to get familiar with combined depth and color images, and explore point clouds in 3D.
You can use any depth sensing device you want. There should be plenty of options in the ER. Your application can be either 2D or 3D (or any-D), but should use depth data as input.</description></item><item><title>Assignment 4</title><link>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/assignment-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 19:18:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/assignment-4/</guid><description>Communication # Instructions # Your assignment is to create two applications and use a communication protocol to exchange information between them.
At least one of your applications needs to be written in openFrameworks. The other can be OF or anything else. You can build off of a previous assignment or class exercise. For example, you can send blobs from the color tracker to a different application to control another object. Make sure to use an appropriate method of communication.</description></item><item><title>Final Project</title><link>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/final-project/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 17:10:27 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://seeingmachines.betamovement.net/docs/assignments/final-project/</guid><description>Create a fully fleshed out interactive. This can take many shapes:
Reactive installation Performance Game Product prototype Something else Fish Hammer from Neil Mendoza on Vimeo. Instructions # Work on your own or with a partner (team of 1 or 2). Project complexity should be proportional to the size of your team. Clearly define everyone&amp;rsquo;s roles. If you have an idea and are looking for a partner, propose it on Discord!</description></item></channel></rss>